Today the Lombard Insurance people have
given safety assurance that they should carry helmet, so
look, I am standing near the gate of
our Agriculture University, near the Rose Garden,
right now I have seen
two-four people there, let me
show you, for this
they are
roaming around [music], it seems to me that
everyone is roaming around here, which is about road safety, so
let us take you along, we will find you somewhere,
friends,
here the technology related to agriculture is
researched,
where no one is visible, there is gate number
two, gate number three, gate number
four
[music],
you will get everything
[music], so I
came to the Agriculture University, then I came to know that
today the Lombard, which is the
ICICI company, they say that
protect yourself, you need
speed at the same time, nice but wearing helmet is always
advised, see, a lot of
people have gathered here, they are
young
and the reason for you is that all the Lombard
companies here are here, or else they are  The seat must have been lost. If you
drive too fast, then this accident will happen.
Drive a scooter, accident will happen. I
found out.
Okay, I do
n't know
why the safety took away the accident. I am here. An accident
just happened in Hyderabad. Those who should wear helmets, so those who have
helmets, I should
drive a little faster. Where was the
accident kept?
Okay.
[Music]
[Laughter]
If I do this for a minute, then
Google will take your photo. That's
right
[Laughter] Do accidents happen by driving
or by walking?
Accidents happen.
What do we have to do for this?
You have to change your attitude.
What problem did you have?
ICICI Lombard, Ludhiana.
This time, let's see how it looked. I showed you this way. I have done this
here.
And quickly, we reached where we are. So
we thought we should show you. Please
subscribe to our channel. Many children are in trouble
here. And the administration here, the
police administration, which controls the traffic,
says that we will do it today, but we
reached late, so there was a little time for the Nano, but
this is 10, you are done.
[Music]
Hello, hello
[Laughter]
Sir, Sir
talked about helmets to the children and their parents. Here, there
is a road safety week organized by ICICI Lombard. ICICI
Lombard's name is Right to Safety.
Within that, we provide helmets to the children and
take insurance from their parents so that they can adopt safe driving
practices on the road so that they can learn from childhood.
[Music]
Safety drive for children is to carry a helmet.
Remember, big and small helmets teach for all. If you are
riding a bike, then give it to them where there are
small bikes and where there is traffic jam.
[Music]
This should really be done. So,
look at the
traffic jams on the roads. How can you stop that traffic jam?
First, first, look at the awareness. We are a city right now, we are
all helping each other, we are contributing to our society, so
we should
not degrade, we should make people understand. So, what
you have said is very good.
Janjir ji, my view is that the
success of the traffic police is not based on the
number
of people, how many people should be made aware, how much
we have told them and made them aware.  And I
created a feeling in them about their safety
and
told them that we should reduce the death rate,
people should go to us, sir,
tell me how did you organize,
what is your name, I would like to know first,
very good, and I have spent 40 years in the Navy
and now I am engaged in this work, so will
you people tell me about someone else or this
Lombard company which makes Spencer,
our organization is Indian
Head Injury Foundation, okay, those who suffer from head or spinal injuries,
starting from awareness, this is the
awareness part, right brother, avoid
accidents, okay, and if an accident happens here, then
we should look after the patients, the biggest reason for
accidents is over speeding, someone is driving well, someone is
driving at 60, so
you will not get any direction here to drive at 40,
drive at 20, and I see this many times  The
speed limit is 40, a
lot of construction is being reduced, so once
this is done,
put up a board saying construction is complete. We have
radars which check the
speed, sometimes we have one and a half,
sometimes it doesn't, I
cannot do this, I know it, sir, I often
see that you people over speed, two-four
people
die every day, this is not enough, there are
small sadkas in Ludhiana, 20 feet, will the police do
something or you, the municipal body, will have to do something,
and I think these people who put up
signs, Irshad,
how many votes do they have, MLA, they all put up hoardings, wishing you a happy
Baisakhi, Happy New Year, do
n't they think that you people should
live your life like this, is this your role
and we are doing it, but you see, he went away after asking you
many questions, sorry
journalist, but we are still asking you questions, then
some day we will sit with you and we will
talk to you more, tell me your name, I
am Commodore Ranbir Talwar and I come every year, so
see, Talwar sahib, see,
from the Navy  He is retired, whenever he comes with this service spirit, he
says that you should control your head,
play your legs and save yourself, do not do race
driving, if you are driving slowly
then there will be no
accident, thank you sir,
thank you very much for
giving me time, okay.